Today we're going to be making a wagon from a shoe box.
And its going to be a really special wagon with wheels that are going to turn.
And I'm going to go through the supplies now that we're going to need to make our wagon.
The first thing that we'll need is twenty four CDs.
They don't have to be new CDs obviously but if you have any laying around the house its a good chance to clean out your office drawers and come up with twenty four CDs that you don't need.
These are going to be the wheels of our wagon.
And then we're going to need a paint brush which will be used to apply the glue to the box and we're going to be covering it with tissue paper.
And we'll need some wooden sticks.
These wooden sticks are usually found, they're used for grilling on a BarBque with a sharp end on one end, and they can come in a super market or craft store.
We're going to need two of these.
These are going to be the axles of the front wheels and back wheels, one for each set of wheels.
We're going to be using masking tape.
And we're going to need an empty tissue roll, a paper towel holder.
This is the roll from the inside.
This is going to be the handle of the wagon and its going to be attached to the wagon with a heavy ribbon which is the purple ribbon you see here.
And we're also going to be decorating the wagon.
For that we're going to either be using, we chose to use some flowers, kind of soft cut up flowers you can get at any craft store.
But you don't necessarily need these kind of decorations.
You can just cut up magazines and find different pictures to paste on the wagon.
And we're going to be using some tissue paper as well to cover the wagon.
And the main body of the wagon is going to be a shoe box.
Now the shoe box should have a, it should have the top along with it, because the top is going to be glued on to the bottom of the base.
And we're also going to need a bowl that we're going to use to mix glue and water.
We want the glue to be a little bit thinner than its normal consistency.
And that's what we're going to be using on the tissue paper to stick it on to the shoe box which is going to be the body of the wagon.
And we're going to need some beads.
We're going to need eight large beads and eight small beads.
These beads are going to be used to hold the wheels on to the wooden sticks on the axle.
And you will need to make sure that the beads are wide enough, the hole inside is wide enough to fit on to the wooden stick which is going to be the, again, the axle of the wheels.
And we'll be using a scissor and its helpful to have a marker and we're going to need some all purpose glue or like a rubber cement type of glue as well.
And these are the supplies needed for the project of making a wagon from a shoe box.